Tao Sor now knows, that he's not my real brother!
I have to do everything to make him forget,
and come back to being the Tao Sor I know!
Why do you have to go this far?
I'm protecting you.
That's not true.
Both you and Mom know well, don't you?
Kim..
where are you?
Come see me.
I'm waiting on the bridge.
Okay, alright.
I'll hurry there.
Wait for me, Tao Sor.
Wait for me.
I thought I was dead, but I was able to wake up.
Then I found out that I've been Sleeping Beauty for over 3 years.
And your son and boyfriend?
My husband lost his life at sea,
as for my son, he was swallowed by the sea, disappearing without a trace.
At first, I couldn't take it.
I tried to find him,
but the officers said it's already been 3 years.
If they could, then they would have already found him.
The boy that this woman is talking about is me?
Yes.
I'm not sure either, but I think so.
So we have hurry and get you to see her.
I promised you, that I would help you find your real mom.
Don't answer.
Let me take you to see your other first,
and then I'll tell you everything.
This way!
We have to got there!
Tao Sor.
I think...
we didn't make it.
So...
What should we do, Kim?
I'm..sorry.
For not being able to find your real mom like I promised.
Don't worry.
From now on,
I'll take care of you.
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me? We're dating, after all.
Let's...go get your things from your house.
How's it going, Talay?
He turbed off his phone.
He looks tired, he might faint somewhere.
I think I should go look for him myself.
Talay, stay with mom.
Calm down, Dad.
He'll be back.
It's you again?
Where'd you take Tao Sor?!
When will you leave Tao Sor's life?
Probably too late now, man.
Because Tao Sor's promised, that he'll stay with me.
Tao Sor, come to Mommy!
Mom?
Just now, I went to go see my mom with Kim.
Hey, Kim.
What lies have you feeding Tao Sor?
I just told him the truth.
Another thing...
he's promised with me that he'll stay with me.
Let's go pack your things.
Look, Tao Sor...
Don't listen to him.
You are my brother.
and these are your parents!
If you don't believe me...
take a look at this.
It's a picture of our family.
Even if you don't remember,
these memories...
hold so much meaning to us.
Tao Sor, you will always be my son.
Don't leave.
Tao Sor.
He's only known you for a few months,
he only thinks about his own needs.
He doesn't care about what you need.
Not true!
Everything I said has been the truth.
And I also want Tao Sor to live his own life.
Not accept that he's just a person you took in.
Tao Sor, let's go.
Tao Sor.
That's enough, Talay.
If you really love Tao Sor,
you'd want him to have his own life.
Just this...
you've already ruined his life far enough.
You're the one that needs to get out.
You have to get out of our lives.
We were doing fine,
but you came and messed with everything.
I will leave!
but Tao Sor's coming with me.
tao Sor's not going anywhere.
This is his home,
his family....
Tao Sor, come with me.
Tao Sor leaves with me!
You're the one that needs to leave.
But Tao Sor's agreed with me.
Tao Sor's decided to go with me!
Tao Sor, stay with me.
That's enough!
I don't know who to trust anymore!
Tao Sor, don't go anywhere!
Tao Sor!
I'll go after him, Mom.
Tao Sor, pleae don't be hurt.
Tao Sor! Can you hear me?
I love you, Tao Sor!
You'll be fine, okay?
Kim.
When will you understand?
Every time he finds out the truth, he turns out like this.
You might think I'm selfish for lying to Tao Sor.
But what good comes from him finding out the truth?
Before you met Tao Sor,
it wasn't like this situation never happened.
In the end, when Tao Sor wakes up.
everything just disappears.
There's just me and my family
who still remember everything.
I beg you, don't tak Tao Sor away from us.
Our family has been broken up enough.
Ever since Tao Sor left.
But him coming back today...
is like a reward for all of us.
Tao Sor...
is important to all of us.
I ask of you, please return Tao Sor to us.
I understand everyone's feelings.
How losing someone can hurt so much.
I also...
lost a brother 10 years ago.
But I've never thought of replacing him.
Because in reality,
no one can really replace anyone else.
Please don't! Don't take Tao Sor away from me!
Don't take Tao Sor away from us.
Mom...
Mom, get up.
Dad, take Mom to go rest.
Take care of your brother.
What does his condition look like?
His body is just exhausted,
like he's been avoiding sleep for several days.
Plus, he has face a stressful situation,
so his body couldn't take it.
But I gave him some meds and gave him an IV, he should be fine soon.
So will this...
have any effect on his memories?
The brain didn't recieve any trauma,
but in the case of memories...
we'll have to take another look when he wakes up.
He might remember everything.
Or...
he might not remember anything,
like how you wanted.
I'm asking seriously,
Don't you get tired?
Of course I do.
But I have to do it.
It's really the best thing for everyone.
If you're tired, you should get some rest.
Thank you so much.
For never leaving me.
You guys...
why isn't everyone asleep?
We were waiting for you.
How was it? Did you see her?
It's okay. I'll find a way to contact her.
No matter what, Tao Sor has to be able to met his real mother.
I think...
you don't have to.
Why are you sighing like that?
Sometimes...
him not being able to remember...
could be a good thing for Tao Sor.
And...
you're gonna just let him forget you so easily?
I'm only here for a year,
I don't see why I have to get attached to anyone.
And can you really forget him, Kim?
Hey.
If you want to cry, just let it out. You don't have to be strong all the time.
Wrong person!
It's not wrong.
It's the same for you.
You don't have to be strong all the time.
You can show some weakness, I won't tell anyone.
To be honest, sometimes...
you don't have to keep forgetting about him.
It's not even your fault.
No one wants things like this to happen.
We should just the remember the good moments,
don't let anyone take those memories away.
I love you, Sang.
I love you too, Kim.
I also love the both of you.
Tao Sor.
Who are you?
What is this place?
And...
who am I?
Your name is Tao Sor.
You're my little brother.
I don't remember that?
It's okay.
It's good that you don't remember.
Hello, Chef Mochi. I'm Daiji.
Oh...
Talay's told me already.
Really?
What did he say?
He said that...
you were my assistant in the kitchen.
You make great international food,
as for me,
I make Thai food and Chinese food.
Anything else?
You are a friend he loves dearly.
And you...
also love me very much.
So what are you doing now?
I'm drawing.
You want me to hang out here with you?
It's okay.
Okay. See you soon, then!
I've come to pay my respects to you.
I apologize for coming so late.
I don't know...if I came here earlier, would you have helped me achieve my wishes in love.
But if I asked you to help me now,
would you help me?
A person like you...
believes in Holy Power too?
What about you?
Did you get anything you asked for?
I asked for Tao Sor to come back.
I won't ask the gods for anything.
But there's something I want to ask from you.
In a few days, I'll be going back to Bangkok.
I want Tao Sor's cooking for my last meal here.
Does it look good, Dad?
It's so cute, Kim.
Did you know?
I love Southern Fish Curry!
Southern Fish Curry?
When did you start liking this?
I've known you all your life, I've never seen you eat this.
Someone showed me how to eat it.
Someone showed you?
Wait till you see my dish!
Happy Birthday, bro!
Hope you stay handsome, get richer, and finally find true love.
That might be a bit hard.
Once I'm back in Bangkok,
would I be able to find anyone?
You find someone.
How's the food?
We haven't had any yet.
Everything looks really good!
Thank you, Talay!
Once I'm back in Bangkok...
I'm gonna miss Phuket food to death.
Enjoy your meal.
Happy Birthday to you,
Make a wish, Sir.
Tao Sor.
Go home.
You wanna go running today?
Can we do something else?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'll have someone clean this up.
Thank you.
Please excuse me.
Thank you..
I don't have a fork.
Here.
Kim, there's another tour for Wat Arun booked for today.
But all the guides are busy, will you take them yourself?
Tell them that we're fully booked for today,
If they want to go, they'll have to book for tomorrow.
Okay.
Kim, shall we go have Phuket food for dinner tonight?
I know that you miss Phuket.
Sure, Mom.
You want to try arranging new trips?
When you were in Phuket, your uncle wouldn't stop complimenting you.
I'd rather not, Mom.
I'm already overwhelmed with the work as is!
Okay, I won't disturb you any longer.
Hello? What's up, Siw?
Someone misses your 1 Day Trip.
Who?
Nao. Who'd you think it was?
Well...
I wasn't thinking of anyone.
Don't play dumb. We're all grown ups here.
So...
by the way, have you been to that resort lately?
Since the day we sent you off, I haven't been back there at all.
Kim, you don't have to keep pushing down the things you don't forget.
Weren't you the one who said that?
I'll go visit when I have time, okay?
Hurry back!
I think there might be someone waiting for you.
He...
might..not remember anything at all.
Oh, Kim.
Don't think like that.
That's all.
Oay, Kim. See you!
Wait here, Tao Sor. I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Tao Sor!
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Oh.
It's nothing.
Tao Sor!
why did you do this?
Let's go.
Bro...
I dreamt of a man...
I don't know who he is...
I hear his voice,
see only his shadow,
but it was so real.
I know him, right?
I give in, Tao Sor.
I'll take you to see him.